<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
  <LocalizedText>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_HOLY_SITE_DL_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>您城市里的宗教祭祀区。若该区域内含有三级宗教建筑，则本城+15% [ICON_Faith] 信仰值。为相邻单元格+1魅力。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_HOLY_SITE_DL_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>A district in your city for religious worship. +15% [ICON_Faith] Faith if there exists a third-tier worship building in the district. +1 Appeal to adjacent tiles.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_LAVRA_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>俄罗斯特色宗教活动区域，代替圣地，建造费用更低。[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]此城市每消耗一位伟人，城市边界则扩张1单元格。若该区域内含有三级宗教建筑，则本城+15% [ICON_Faith] 信仰值。为相邻单元格+1魅力。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_LAVRA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>A district unique to Russia for religious activity. Replaces the Holy Site district and cheaper to build.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Your city border grows by one tile each time a Great Person is expended in this city. +15% [ICON_Faith] Faith if there exists a third-tier worship building in the district. +1 Appeal to adjacent tiles.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_HANSA_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>德国特色工业区域，替代工业区，建造费用更低。[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]可从每个相邻的运河和堤坝区域处获得+2 [ICON_Production] 生产力加成。可从每个相邻的商业中心、水渠区域处获得+1 [ICON_Production] 生产力加成。每2处相邻资源为其提供1点 [ICON_Production] 生产力加成。每两处相邻区域为其提供1点 [ICON_Production] 生产力加成。随着科技和市政的发展，其将获得更多的相邻 [ICON_Production] 生产力加成。为相邻单元格-1魅力。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_HANSA_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>A district unique to Germany for industrial activity. Replaces the Industrial Zone district and cheaper to build.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_Production] Production bonus for each adjacent Canal, and Dam districts. +1 [ICON_Production] Production bonus for each adjacent Commercial Hub, Aqueduct districts. +1 [ICON_Production] Production bonus for every two adjacent resources. +1 [ICON_Production] Production bonus for every two adjacent district tiles. Additional adjacency [ICON_Production] Production bonus as you advance through the Technology and Civics Tree. -1 Appeal to adjacent tiles.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_AQUEDUCT_DL_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>区域从相邻河流、湖泊、绿洲或山脉引水，为该城市提供淡水资源。没有淡水资源的城市最多获得6个 [ICON_Housing] 住房。相反，已有淡水资源的城市 [ICON_Housing] 住房数量+2；若与地热裂缝相邻，提供+1 [ICON_Amenities] 宜居度。干旱时可防止 [ICON_Food] 食物损失。本城所有淡水或相邻水渠的农田+1 [ICON_FOOD] 食物。[NEWLINE] 必须修建在与市中心相邻的单元格中。军事工程师可消耗1次使用次数来完成水渠20%的修建进度。但1个城市只允许建造1个。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_AQUEDUCT_DL_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>A district that provides this city with a source of fresh water from an adjacent River, Lake, Oasis, or Mountain. Cities that do not yet have existing fresh water receive up to 6 [ICON_Housing] Housing. Cities that already have existing fresh water will instead get +2 [ICON_Housing] Housing. If built adjacent to a Geothermal Fissure +1 [ICON_Amenities] Amenity. Prevents [ICON_Food] Food loss during Drought. All farm adjacent to fresh water or Aqueduct +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food. [NEWLINE] Must be built adjacent to the City Center. Military Engineers can spend a charge to complete 20% of an Aqueduct's production.One per city.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_BATH_EXPANSION2_ALT_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>促进城市发展的罗马特色区域。取代水渠，建造费用更低。[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]从相邻河流、湖泊、绿洲或山脉引水，为该城市提供淡水资源。尚未拥有淡水资源的城市最多获得6个 [ICON_Housing] 住房。已有淡水资源的城市则+2 [ICON_Housing] 住房。若与地热裂缝相邻，提供+1 [ICON_Amenities] 宜居度。在任何情况下，浴场都能额外提供+2 [ICON_Housing] 住房和+1 [ICON_Amenities] 宜居度。干旱时可防止 [ICON_Food] 食物损失。必须修建在与市中心相邻的单元格中。本城所有淡水或相邻浴场的农田+1 [ICON_FOOD] 食物。[NEWLINE] 军事工程师可消耗1次使用次数来完成浴场20%的修建进度。但1个城市只允许建造1个。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_BATH_EXPANSION2_ALT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>A district unique to Rome for city growth. Replaces the Aqueduct district and cheaper to build.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]It provides this city with a source of fresh water from an adjacent River, Lake, Oasis, or Mountain. Cities that do not yet have existing fresh water receive up to 6 [ICON_Housing] Housing. Cities that already have existing fresh water will instead get +2 [ICON_Housing] Housing. If built adjacent to a Geothermal Fissure +1 [ICON_Amenities] Amenity. In all cases the Bath provides an additional bonus of +2 [ICON_Housing] Housing and +1 [ICON_Amenities] Amenity. Prevents [ICON_Food] Food loss during Drought. Must be built adjacent to the City Center. Military Engineers can spend a charge to complete 20% of a Bath's production.All farm adjacent to fresh water or Bath +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food. [NEWLINE] Must be built adjacent to the City Center. Military Engineers can spend a charge to complete 20% of an Aqueduct's production.One per city.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_HARBOR_DL_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>城市中的海军活动区域。同时取消从该单元格上下船的 [ICON_Movement] 移动力消耗。必须修建在和陆地相邻的海岸或湖泊单元格上。无法建造在礁石上。[NEWLINE] +2 [ICON_HOUSING] 住房。为本城的渔船 +1 [ICON_FOOD] 食物。对所有海军单位+25% [ICON_PRODUCTION] 生产力。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_HARBOR_DL_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>A district for naval activity in your city. Also removes the [ICON_Movement] Movement penalty for embarking and disembarking to and from this tile. Must be built on Coast or Lake Terrain adjacent to land. Cannot be built on Reef. +2 [ICON_HOUSING] Housing. Fishing Boats +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food in this city. +25% [ICON_PRODUCTION] production towards all naval units.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_COTHON_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>腓尼基特色城市海军活动区域，取代港口且建造成本更低。必须修建在海岸或与陆地相邻的湖泊地貌上。[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]该城市的海军单位与开拓者的 [ICON_PRODUCTION] 生产力+50%。在该城范围内，所有受损海军单位每回合可恢复100点生命值。[NEWLINE] +2 [ICON_HOUSING] 住房。为本城的渔船 +1 [ICON_FOOD] 食物。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_COTHON_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text> A district unique to Phoenicia for naval activity in your city. Replaces the Harbor district and cheaper to build. Must be built on Coast or Lake Terrain adjacent to land.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+50% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production towards naval units and Settlers in this city. All wounded naval units in this city’s borders heal +100 HP each turn.+2 [ICON_HOUSING] Housing. Fishing Boats +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food in this city.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_ROYAL_NAVY_DOCKYARD_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>城市中的英国特色海军活动区域，取代港口且建造成本更低。同时移除该单元格的上船、下船 [ICON_Movement] 移动力减益。必须建在与陆地相邻的海岸或湖泊地形上。[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]造船厂中建造的所有海军单位+1 [ICON_Movement] 移动力。[NEWLINE]修建在外国大陆上时+2 [ICON_Gold] 金币、每回合的忠诚度+4。无法建造在礁石上。[NEWLINE] +2 [ICON_HOUSING] 住房。为本城的渔船 +1 [ICON_FOOD] 食物。对所有海军单位+25% [ICON_PRODUCTION] 生产力。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_ROYAL_NAVY_DOCKYARD_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>A district unique to England for naval activity in your city. Replaces the Harbor district. Also removes the [ICON_Movement] Movement penalty for embarking and disembarking to and from this tile. Must be built on Coast or Lake Terrain adjacent to land.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_Movement] Movement for all naval units built in Dockyard[NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_Gold] Gold and +4 Loyalty per turn when built on a foreign continent. Cannot be built on Reef.+2 [ICON_HOUSING] Housing. Fishing Boats +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food in this city. +25% [ICON_PRODUCTION] production towards all naval units.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_IKANDA_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>祖鲁特色区域，替代军营。+2 [ICON_Housing] 住房。解锁相应的市政或科技后即可生产军团和军队。创建军团和军队的速度更快。[NEWLINE] 生产陆地军事单位+30% [ICON_PRODUCTION] 生产力。为本城已开发的[ICON_RESOURCE_STONE] 石头+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] 生产力。为相邻单元格-1魅力。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_IKANDA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text> A district unique to Zulu which replaces the Encampment. Provides +2 [ICON_Housing] Housing. Once the Civic or Technology prerequisite is met, Corps and Armies can be built outright. Faster Corps and Army creation.[NEWLINE] +30% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production towards Land Military Units. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for improved [ICON_RESOURCE_STONE] Stone in this city. -1 Appeal to adjacent tiles.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_ENCAMPMENT_DL_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>您城市里的军事机构区。[NEWLINE] 生产陆地军事单位+15% [ICON_PRODUCTION] 生产力。为本城的已开发的 [ICON_RESOURCE_STONE] 石头+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] 生产力。为相邻单元格-1魅力。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_ENCAMPMENT_DL_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text> A district in your city for military facilities.[NEWLINE] +15% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production towards Land Military Units. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for improved [ICON_RESOURCE_STONE] Stone in this city. -1 Appeal to adjacent tiles.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MBANZA_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text> 刚果特色区域，只能建在雨林或树林里。代替社区，可更早建造，且建造费用更低。无视魅力值，固定提供+5 [ICON_Housing] 住房、+3 [ICON_Food] 食物和+5 [ICON_Gold] 金币。为相邻的雨林和森林单元格 +1 [ICON_FOOD] 食物。允许使用 [ICON_Faith] 信仰值购买开拓者和建造者。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MBANZA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text> A district unique to Kongo that can only be constructed in Rainforest or Woods. Replaces the Neighborhood district but is available earlier and cheaper to build. Provides +5 [ICON_Housing] Housing , +3 [ICON_Food] Food, and + 5 [ICON_Gold] Gold, regardless of Appeal. +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food to all adjacent Forest and Rainforest tiles. Allows the purchasing of Settlers and Builders using [ICON_Faith] Faith.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_AERODROME_DL_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>可用于建造和存放飞机的区域。不能建在丘陵上。建造不受人口限制。建造空中单位时，+25% [Icon_Production] 生产力。为相邻单元格+1魅力。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_AERODROME_DL_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>A district that allows you to build and store aircraft. Cannot be built on Hills. Can be built regardless of number of citizens. +25% [Icon_Production] Production towards Air Units. -1 Appeal to adjacent tiles. </Text>
    </Replace> 
  	<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_DIPLOMATIC_QUARTER_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text> 通过外交，外国文明的每个代表团或大使馆将为您的文明提供+1 [ICON_FAVOR] 外交支持。如建在市中心旁，则+1 [ICON_ENVOY] 使者。敌方间谍将此区域和相邻区域当做目标时，其效果将降低2级。文明中一次仅限建造一座此区域。可额外招募一名间谍。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_DIPLOMATIC_QUARTER_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Your civilization receives +1 [ICON_FAVOR] Diplomatic Favor for each Delegation or Embassy from a foreign civilization through diplomacy. +1 [ICON_ENVOY] Envoy if built next to the city center. Enemy Spies operate at 2 levels below normal targeting this district and adjacent districts. Only 1 can exist in your empire at a time. Grants the ability to construct an additional Spy.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_THANH_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text> 越南特色区域，替代“军营”。每与1个区域相邻，则+2 [ICON_CULTURE] 文化值。研究完“飞行”科技后，将获得与 [ICON_CULTURE] 文化值产量相等的 [ICON_TOURISM] 旅游业绩。此区域不需要人口、建造花费更低、无法建在市中心周围，也并非专业化区域。[NEWLINE]每个城市只允许建造1个。给相邻单元格-1魅力。生产陆地军事单位+15% [ICON_PRODUCTION] 生产力。为本城已开发的 [ICON_RESOURCE_STONE] 石头+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] 生产力。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_THANH_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>A district unique to Vietnam which replaces the Encampment. +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture for each adjacent district. After Flight is researched receive [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism equal to the [ICON_CULTURE] Culture output. This district does not require population, is cheaper to build, cannot be built adjacent to the city center, and is not a specialty district.[NEWLINE]One per city. -1 Appeal to adjacent tiles. +15% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production towards Land Military Units. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for improved [ICON_RESOURCE_STONE] Stone in this city.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_ACROPOLIS_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN"> 
		<Text>希腊特色文化遗址区域，替代剧院广场，建造费用更低。建成后奖励1名 [ICON_Envoy] 使者。[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]每个相邻区域+1 [ICON_Culture] 文化值，每个相邻市中心额外+2 [ICON_Culture] 文化值。每个相邻奇观、娱乐设施及水上乐园+2 [ICON_Culture] 文化值。只能建在丘陵上。为相邻单元格+1魅力。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_ACROPOLIS_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>A district unique to Greece for cultural sites. Replaces the Theater Square district and cheaper to build. Awards 1 [ICON_Envoy] Envoy when completed.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_Culture] Culture bonus for each adjacent district and an additional +2[ICON_Culture] Culture bonus for adjacent City Center. +2 [ICON_Culture] Culture bonus for each adjacent wonder, Entertainment Complex, and Water Park. Can only be built on Hills. +1 Appeal to adjacent tiles. </Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_PRESERVE_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>可基于魅力最高提供3点 [ICON_Housing] 住房。对相邻的中立单元格施放文化炸弹，使相邻单元格+2魅力。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_PRESERVE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Grants up to 3 [ICON_Housing] Housing based on Appeal. Culture bombs adjacent neutral tiles, and increases their Appeal by 2.</Text>
    </Replace>
  </LocalizedText>
</GameData>
