<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
  <LocalizedText>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_BUILDER_DL_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>可建造单元格改良设施、移除地貌（如森林或雨林），或收获资源。建造者可使用4次。可通过政策或奇观（如金字塔）增加使用次数。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_BUILDER_DL_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>May create tile improvements, remove features like Woods or Rainforest, or Harvest some resources. Builders can be used 4 times. This can be increased through policies or wonders like the Pyramids.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_SIEGE_TOWER_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>中世纪支援单位。与城市相邻时，近战、抗骑兵单位和武僧可无视城墙直接对城市发起进攻。对拥有文艺复兴城墙的城市无效。对现代城市防御无效。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_SIEGE_TOWER_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Medieval era support unit. When adjacent to a city, attacking melee, anti-cavalry units and Warrior Monks ignore Walls and immediately assault the city. Does not affect cities with Renaissance Walls. Ineffective against Urban Defenses.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_BATTERING_RAM_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>远古时代支援单位。与城市相邻时，近战，抗骑兵单位和武僧发起进攻可对城墙输出全额伤害。对拥有中世纪或文艺复兴城墙的城市无效。对现代城市防御无效。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_BATTERING_RAM_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Ancient era support unit. When adjacent to a city, attacking melee and anti-cavalry units do full damage to the city’s Walls. Does not affect cities with Medieval or Renaissance Walls. Ineffective against Urban Defenses.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_MILITARY_ENGINEER_ALT_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>中世纪支援单位。需要“兵工厂”才能生产。能建造道路、堡垒、飞机跑道、导弹发射井和穿山隧道改良设施。其建造次数可用于加快运河、堤坝、水渠区域或拦洪坝20%的建造进度。拥有无视地形和河流的特技。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_MILITARY_ENGINEER_ALT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Medieval era support unit. Requires an Armory to produce. Can construct Roads, Railroads, Forts, Airstrips, Missile Silos, and Mountain Tunnel improvements. One of their build charges can also be used to complete 20% of a Canal, Dam or Aqueduct district or a Flood Barrier building. Can move with ability that ignore all the terrain and river.</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_WARRIOR_MONK_DESCRIPTION" Language="zh_Hans_CN">
      <Text>高移动力的古典陆地战斗单位，拥有独特的升级树。只能在有寺庙的城市通过 [ICON_FAITH] 信仰购买。</Text>
    </Replace>
    <Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_WARRIOR_MONK_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Fast-moving land combat unit with a unique promotion tree. Can only be purchased by [ICON_FAITH] Faith in city with a Temple. </Text>
    </Replace>
  </LocalizedText>
</GameData>
